TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
새 메일이 도착했습니다.
A new mail has arrived.
읽어.
Read.
여긴 데스 메다로트 사 영업 본부. 음양 마을에 보낸 당사 제품, 독점 판매 계획의 진행을 보고해 주십시오.
This is the sales headquarters of Death Medarot Company.
Please report on our company's products and the progress of exclusive sales plan.
오늘 데스 메다로트에 의한 메다로트 일제 출격 작전의 결과는, 내일 지금쯤은 음양의 모든 메다로트는 기능 정지되어 있을 터.
The result of Death Medarot Simultaneous Mobilization Plan will lead all the Medarots in Ginjou to stop working.
예. 보고를 마칩니다.
Understood. End of report.
자, 슬슬 우리의 실력을 알려 줄게, 텐료 잇키.
Now it's time to show our true capabilities, Tenryo Ikki.
음양 마을 메다로트 전멸 작전 시작.
Start Ginjou Village Medarot Annihilation Plan.
수수께끼의 도쿠스 사용자
Mysterious Dorcus Wielder
(en: Who is the Mystery Medafighter?!)
쳇, 아직 아무도 안 왔네.
Tch, nobody's here yet.
뭐야?
Who is it?
어?
Huh?
GLT형 가이로트
GLT Type Gairot
뭔 짓이야!
What are you doing?!
블루즈독!
Bluesdog!
아게다마!
Agedama!
뭐, 뭐야, 너희들!
W- who are you guys?!
뭔 볼 일이야?
What do you have against us?
뭔 말이라도 해 봐!
Say something!
잠깐! 너도 메다로터야?
You there! You must be a Medarotter, right?
메다로터라면 도와줘!
If you are one, then help me!
뭐야! 안 구해줄 거야?
What's that?! You aren't going to help me?!
저건 분명 데스 메다로트.
That was Death Medarot.
도쿠스 전송.
Transfer Dorcus.
네 차례다, 도쿠스.
It's your turn, Dorcus.
KWG형 도쿠스
KWG Type Dorcus
예, 마스터.
Yessir, master.
공격 준비!
Prepare to attack!
잠깐!
Wait!
잇키!
Ikki!
오래 기다렸지?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
딱히 기다린 거 아닌데.
I didn't even wait, actually.
어...
Err...
텐료 잇키!
Tenryo Ikki!
헤! 1대 2로 로보틀을 걸다니 어지간히 실력에 자신이 없나 봐!
Heh! Trying to do a 1:2 Robattle? You must be very diffident of your skills!
뭐야?!
What?!
-아리카, 같이 하자!
-알았어!
-Arika, let's do this together!
-Of course!
-가자!
-네!
-Let's do this!
-Got it!
여긴 모모카와! 작전 진행중인 전 가이로트, 집합해라!
Momokawa here! All Gairots performing the plan, assemble!
뭐, 뭐야, 이거?
W- what's this?!
둘러싸였어!
We're surrounded!
젠장! 어디서 모인 거야, 이 장구벌레 놈들은!
Dammit! Where did these maggots come from?!
어? 장구벌레? 시, 시끄러워!
What?! Maggot?! S- shut up!
가이로트, 공격 준비!
Gairots, prepare to attack!
어째, 잇키?
What should we do, Ikki?
어?
Huh?
공격 개시!
Commence attack!
뭐, 뭐야?!
W- what?!
약자를 괴롭히면 안 된다. 데스 메다로트 나부랭아.
You must not tease weaklings, you Death Medarot garbage.
야, 약자를 괴롭힌다고?!
H- he's teasing weaklings?!
누, 누구냐!
W- who are you?!
가라, 도쿠스.
Go, Dorcus.
예, 마스터.
Yessir, master.
뭐야?!
What?!
대단해!
Awesome!
젠장!
Damn!
고마워.
Thank you.
도와줘서.
For helping, that is.
딱히 너희들을 도와준 건 아니다.
I didn't help you.
싸우고 싶으니까 싸웠고 그 뿐이다.
I fought because I wanted to, and that's all about it.
그래라.
Yeah, sure.
가자, 도쿠스.
Let's go, Dorcus.
예, 마스터.
Yessir, master.
좋아! 특종 잡았다!
Yeah! I got a story!
약자? 이 내가?
Weakling? Me?
그치? 그 소년이 눈 깜빡할 새에 10대나 처리했다고!
You wouldn't believe this! That boy got rid of all 10 of them in the blink of an eye!
그렇게 강해?
Is he that strong?
-그야 당연하지!
-흥! 내 로보틀에 멋대로 끼어들고 말야!
-Of course!
-Hmph! He just got in my way during a Robattle!
끼어드는 것보다는 구해진 거겠지.
More like, he saved you, rather than getting in your way.
시꺼! 누가 도와달라 부탁하기라도 했냐!
Quiet! Nobody asked him to help!
잇키, 가끔은 겸허해질 줄도 알아라.
Ikki, you gotta be modest sometimes.
메, 메타비! 너까지!
M- Metabee! You too?!
그래도 그렇게 강한 메다로터, 이 마을에 있었어?
But still, was a Medarotter that strong in this village?
처음 보는 얼굴이긴 했어.
It was my first time seeing him.
아, 사진 찍었으니까 이따 볼래?
Oh, I took a picture. Wanna take a look later?
어? 사진?
Huh? A picture?
그래. 특종.
Yeah. It's a scoop!
특종이구나.
A scoop. Right.
모모카와 군, 가이로트 군단을 네게 맡긴 건 데스 메다로트의 강함을 모두에게 알게 해 주길 바랐기 때문이야.
Momokawa, the reason I entrusted Gairot Force to you is to make everyone know about the strength of Death Medarot.
네, 네...
Y- yes...
데스 메다로트는 최고의 장난감이야. 강함만을 목적으로 개발된 거니까 말야.
Death Medarot is the best toy ever. It is developed solely for strength, you know.
그러면 모두 데스 메다로트를 원하게 될 거야. 약한 메다로트 따위는 아무도 안 사게 될 거야.
Then everyone will want Death Medarot. Nobody will buy weak Medarots.
네.
Yessir.
난 지금 얘들 장난같은 로보틀을 하는 얘들에게 알려주고 싶어.
I want to show them who do Robattles like child's play.
규칙 없는 전투의 즐거움을 말야. 그러니까 네가 지면 곤란해.
The fun of battles without rules, that is. That's why you must not lose.
죄, 죄송합니다.
I- I'm sorry.
그래서 상대는 어떤 놈이야?
So, how was your enemy like?
아, 아무튼, 갑자기 나타난 데다가 재빨라서...
A- anyway, they appeared out of nowhere and were so swift...
-기억 안 나?
-네, 네...
-Don't you remember?
-Y- yeah...
아, 그래.
Oh well.
죄, 죄송합니다.
I- I apologize.
코쿠류 도련님께 손님이 왔습니다.
There are visitors for you, Kokuryu.
안녕안녕안녕안녕!
Hihihihi!
뭔 일이야?
What's up?
귀하의 가이로트를 쓰러뜨린 수수께끼의 메다로터 사진, 어때요?
Would you want a picture of the mysterious Medarotter that took your Gairot down?
가지고 있어?
Do you have it?
예. 지금 여기엔 없지만요.
Yeah. But not now, though.
응, 그럼 그 쪽 조건은?
I see. So what's the condition?
그! 제 페퍼캣도 귀하의 가이로트처럼 날거나 하면 멋지겠다, 하고 생각해서요!
If my Peppercat could fly like your Gairot, that would be cool! That's what I thought!
부유 파트 말이야?
You mean, floating parts?
네!
Yeah!
-좋아. 그 대신
-녀석 사진을!
-Good. In exchange of that,
-his picture!
가능한 빨리.
As soon as possible.
예!
Roger!
수수께끼의 메다로터라.
A mysterious Medarotter, eh?
그래도, 아리카 사진, 간단히 우리에게 줄지요!
But I wonder if Arika will give that picture to us that easily!
안 넘겨주겠지.
Of course she won't.
그럼 어째요?
Then what should we do?
탈취하면 되지.
We'll plunder.
타, 탈취?!
P- plunder?!
네 블루즈독의 원수 갚고 싶지 않냐!
Don't you want to pay back for your Bluesdog?!
워, 원수?!
P- pay back?!
스크류즈가 받은 원수는 스크류즈가 갚는다!
Screws will pay back whenever someone attacks Screws!
그걸 위해서도 페퍼캣의 파워업이 정말 필요해!
For that too, Peppercat really needs a powerup!
대체 언제까지 잇키나 코쿠류한테 잘난척만 당할쏘냐!
We can't be treated lowly from Ikki or Kokuryu forever!
두, 두목!
B- boss!
됐어!
It's done!
그래서 어때?
So how's that?
어...
Hmm...
뭐야, 감질나게. 찍혔어, 안 찍혔어?
Why are you hiding that from me? Is the picture there, or not?
아니, 찍히긴 찍혔는데...
Well, I did, but...
어?
Huh?
스크류즈!
Screws!
좋아! 고맙다!
Great! Thanks!
-재냬 고양이냐?
-감탄할 때냐!
-Are they cats?
-Are you praising them?!
아, 그치! 쫓자, 메타비!
Oh, right! Let's get them, Metabee!
어!
Right!
고, 고양이 이상이야!
T- they are more than cats!
멈춰!
Stop!
재냬, 저렇게 사이 좋았어?
Were they that friendly with each others?!
목적이 같으니까 그렇겠지, 분명! 나쁜 놈들은 잘 달린대잖아!
It's probably because they're thinking about a same thing! You know, bad guys run quickly!
조, 조심해!
W- watch out!
메, 메타비, 부탁해.
M- Metabee, you do the rest.
레클리스 모드!
Reckless Mode!
엄, 맡겨 둬!
Uh, leave it to me!
두, 두목! 이대로는!
B- boss! It's not good!
이랴!
Got you!
카가미야마, 오른쪽, 이와노이, 왼쪽, 나, 직진!
Kagamiyama, right, Iwanoi, left, I, forward!
로저!
Roger!
놓쳤다!
I lost 'em!
대단해... 달아나는 것만은 세계 제일이야.
Awesome... They're the best at running away in the world.
이게 사진이다. 자, 파트를.
This is the picture. Now, show me the parts.
파트는 줄 거니까 일단 사진부터.
I'll give you the parts, but pictures first.
너희들, 날 속일 생각이었어?
Were you people trying to fool me?
뭐?!
What?!
이건 어디의 누군지 알 수 있을 리가 없잖아.
There is no way I can figure out who is this and where is this guy from.
너, 알고 있었지? 여기에 오기 전에 안 봤을 리가 없잖아.
You did know, right? It's improbable that you didn't take a look before coming here.
이걸론 파트를 줄 수 없어.
I can't give you the parts with this.
그런 게 어디 있어! 고생했어! 잇키하고 메타비가 끈질기게 쫓아와서 뿌리치느라!
No way! We've worked so hard, especially because Ikki and Metabee chased us so persistently!
잇키?
Ikki?
녀석들도 수수께끼의 메다로터를 찾고 있었어.
They were looking for that mysterious Medarotter, too.
왜?
Why?
구해진 게 마음에 안 든대. 그 수수께끼의 메다로터에게.
He doesn't like that he has been rescued by that mysterious Medarotter.
그렇구나. 텐료 잇키 말이지?
I see. That Tenryo Ikki, eh?
이건 재밌어졌네.
This just got interesting.
어? 너 전학생이구나! 이름은!
Oh, you must be a transfer student! What's your name?
유즈루라고 해요.
My name is Yuzuru.
여름방학이 끝나면 음양 초등학교에 들어가게 될 거에요.
When the summer vacation is over, I'll be entering Ginjou Elementary School.
좋아! 모르는 게 있으면 내가 뭐든지 알려 줄게!
Great! If there is anything that you don't know, ask me and I'll tell you everything!
거 참, 기쁘네요!
Oh dear, that's great to hear!
아! 스크류즈!
Hey! Screws!
나, 이제 지쳤어!
I'm tired already!
나도. 앞으로 89매나 있어요.
Me too. There are 89 more of these to go.
씨부렁대지 말고 읽어 봐.
Don't complain and read this.
도전장.
Challenge request.
수수께끼의 메다로터에게.
To Mysterious Medarotter.
숨지 말고 이 나님하고 로보틀 승부다!
Don't hide and Have a Robattle match with Me!
그게 아니면 나님이 무서운 거냐, 겁쟁이 놈.
Or, are you Scared of Me, you Coward?
분하면 오늘 5시에 도부로크 언덕의 공터에 와 주십시오.
If this made you Angry, then Please come to the vacant Lot on Doburoku hill.
잘 부탁드립니다.
I am looking Forwards for this.
텐료 잇키가.
From Tenryo Ikki.
자, 완벽하지? 잇키의 멍청함도 가감없이 잘 되어 있고! 내가 한 것 치고 감탄스러워!
Isn't it perfect? It displays Ikki's stupidity as-is! It's so wonderful even for my work!
누가 멍청하냐?
Who's stupid?
이, 잇키! 언제!
I- Ikki! When did you show up?!
아까부터.
From some time ago.
아무리 나라고 해도, 제대로 된 문서 정도는 쓸 줄 알아!
Even for me, I can write a proper document!
고쳐 써!
Rewrite!
아니, 잇키, 그런 게 아니라.
No, Ikki, you're missing the point.
어차피 코쿠류 꿍꿍이겠지! 나하고 그 수수께끼의 메다로터가 싸우게 하려는!
It's probably a plot of Kokuryu to make that mysterious Medarotter and I fight!
그래도 이번엔 코쿠류한테 고마워하겠어.
But for this time, I gotta thank Kokuryu.
난 어떻게든 그 녀석하고 싸워 보아야만 하겠어!
I gotta fight with him no matter what!
-왜?
-왜, 왜라니...
-Why?
-W- why, eh?
뭐, 프라이드 문제겠지.
It's about his pride.
-프, 프라이드?
-어, 그치! 사내 놈 고집이지!
-P- pride?
-Yeah, you heard it right! A stubbornness of a man!
그렇구나! 프라이드를 건 사내 간의 싸움이네, 메타비!
I see! It's a fight between two men overthe pride, Metabee!
음, 오늘 너희들 왠지 멋지네.
Hmm, you two look cool today.
좋아! 우리 스크류즈도 지금부터 잇키와 메타비의 동료다!
Alright! We, Screws, are friends of Ikki and Metabee from now on!
코쿠류한테 굽실굽실거리며 포스터 붙이기 따위 하고 있는 것도 질렸다!
I'm fed up with cringing to Kokuryu and putting posters!
가자! 도부로쿠 언덕에!
Let's go to Doburoku Hill!
왔다!
They're here!
잇키다!
It's Ikki!
어이, 오래 기다렸지! 어?
Hey, thanks for applauding for me! Huh?
뭐가 오래 기다렸지냐? 그보다도 괜찮은 거야?
Again, nobody applauded for you. Anyway, are you okay with this?
-뭐가?
-그러니까, 상대는 그 수수께끼의 메다로터잖아.
-What exactly?
-You know, your opponent is that mysterious Medarotter.
이길 자신 있어?
Are you confident that you'll win?
있어.
Yeah.
뭔가 생각해뒀나 보네.
Then you must be having a plan!
생각 없어.
No plan.
어?
What?!
괜찮다니까! 난 실전에서 강해! 때가 되면 뭔가 생각나겠지!
Again, I'm alright! I'm strong when in times of need! I'll come up with something when I have to!
왔다!
He came!
-저 녀석이...
-수수께끼의 메다로터?
-Is that guy
-the mysterious Medarotter?
가자, 메타비!
Let's go, Metabee!
그래!
Yeah!
네가 수수께끼의 메다로터냐!
Are you the mysterious Medarotter?!
맘대로 불러라.
Call me in whatever name you want.
나하고 로보틀로 승부다!
Have a Robattle with me!
-안됐지만 거절한다.
-뭐?!
-Too bad, but I refuse.
-What?!
내 상대는 데스 메다로트 뿐이다.
My opponent is Death Medarot only.
데스 메다로트?
Death Medarot?
그렇다. 어떤 수를 써서라도 상대를 쓰러뜨리면 될 뿐이라는 다툼의 도구에.
Right. They are tools for quarrel, whose objective is solely to take an opponent down and nothing else.
오늘 아침 모두의 메다로트를 덮친 것도 데스 메다로트의 짓이다.
It is also Death Medarots who attacked everyone's Medarots today morning.
-그 가이로트가?
-데스 메다로트야?
-Are those Gairots
-Death Medarot?
이기기 위해서라면 어떤 더러운 수라도 쓰는 것. 그것이 데스 메다로트의 방식이다.
Using any means even if it's dirty in order to win is the way of Death Medarots.
그게 뭐가 나빠? 로보틀은 이기는 게 전부잖아. 그거 외에 뭐가 있어? 강한 게 뭐가 나빠?
What's so bad about that? Winning is all in a Robattle. Does it mean anything else? What's bad about being strong?
강해? 너희 데스 메다로트가 강하다고?
Strong? You call your Death Medarots strong?
그래. 데스 메다로트가 있으면 더 이상 로보틀에서 져서 분할 필요도 없어.
Yeah. With Death Medarots, nobody won't be regretful because one lost in a Robattle.
좋아. 그럼 날 쓰러뜨리고 데스 메다로트가 강하다는 걸 보여주어 보아라.
Well then. Take me down and show everyone that Death Medarots are strong.
좋아. 프론트라인, 전송.
Great. Transfer Frontline.
FRL형 프론트라인
FRL Type Frontline
하자.
Let's do this.
잠깐 기다려라!
Stop right there!
코쿠류! 저리 가! 수수께끼의 메다로터는 우리하고 싸울 거야!
Kokuryu! Get lost! That mysterious Medarotter is going to fight us!
그래!
He's right!
모모카와.
Momokawa.
잇키, 잠깐 거기 가만히 있어라.
Ikki, stay there still for a moment.
젠장!
Damn it!
가라, 도쿠스.
Go, Dorcus.
예, 마스터.
Yessir, Master.
지금이다. 접근해라.
Now. Approach.
총탄 전송.
Transfer bullets.
회피.
Evade.
접근전이다, 도쿠스.
Begin melee, Dorcus.
츠라누키, 전송!
Transfer Tsuranuki!
젠장! 10대 1이야?!
Damn! Ten vs. one?!
브라스!
Brass!
이걸로 10대 2야.
Now it's 10 versus 2.
니들!
You guys!
이걸로 10대 5지?
This makes 10 vs. 5.
다, 다들!
E- everyone!
이거, 코쿠류가.
This. From Kokuryu.
13대 2야!
It's 13 vs. 2!
어?
Huh?
좋아, 좋네! 멋져!
It's good! It's great! Cool!
더, 더러워!
Y- youre dirty!
가라! 신생 페퍼캣!
Go! Newly born Peppercat!
아직 적응 안 됐는데!
I'm not used to this yet!
-주제넘은 짓 마!
-흥, 잇키를 쓰러뜨리는 건 이 키쿠히메다.
-Don't butt in!
-Hmph, the one to take Ikki down is me, Kikuhime!
어이, 야!
H- hey!
처, 철수!
R- retreat!
이랴!
Take this!
이제 얜 어째?
What should I do with her?
뭐, 이번엔 용서해 줘! 쟤 덕분에 이겼잖아.
You can forgive her this time! She brought us victory, you know.
누, 누가 멈춰 줘!
S- somebody stop me!
오, 오지 마! 저리 가!
D- don't come this way! G- go that way!
살려줘!
Help!
왜 이렇게 되었을까...
Why did this happen...
틀렸네, 이거.
Well, that was short.
찔러라, 도쿠스.
Pierce, Dorcus.
너무해.
That's cruel.
메가배럴, 전송!
Transfer Megabarrel!
뭐야?!
What?!
쏴!
Shoot!
관둬!
Stop it!
승부 났네.
The match is over.
아직이다. 일어서라, 도쿠스!
Not yet. Stand up, Dorcus!
싸워, 싸워라, 도쿠스!
Fight! Keep fighting, Dorcus!
끝장이야.
Time to finish.
싸워, 프론트라인!
Fight, Frontline!
왜 그러냐, 도쿠스!
What's wrong, Dorcus?
그만! 이제 그만해!
Stop! Please stop!
그래. 그 기세야, 도쿠스.
Good. That's it, Dorcus.
쓰러뜨려, 쳐부숴, 프론트라인!
Destroy! Smash up, Frontline!
해라! 지지 마라, 도쿠스!
Do it! Do not lose, Dorcus!
이제 그만둬! 이런 건 로보틀이 아니야!
You can stop now! This is not a Robattle!
아까 너 데스 메다로트 따위, 그냥 다투기 위한 로보틀 따위 싫다고 했잖아!
You said that you hate Death Medarots and Robattles purely for quarreling!
-어.
-그럼 저건 뭐야!
-Yeah.
-Then what's that?!
이런 건 그냥 다툼일 뿐이잖아! 데스 메다로트하고 다를 게 없잖아!
This is just a quarrel! It is not different from Death Medarots at all!
뭐?!
What?!
이게 진짜 로보틀이야, 텐료 잇키 군.
This is the true Robattle, Tenryo Ikki.
너희들은 메다로트를 써서 그냥 다투기를...
You guys are using Medarots just to quarrel...
로보틀은 그런 게 아니야!
Robattles are not like that!
이제 됐어. 돌아가자, 도쿠스.
That's enough. Let's go back, Dorcus.
어, 어이! 왜 그래? 아직 승부 안 났어.
H- hey! What are you doing? The match isn't set yet!
도쿠스? 꽤 실력 있지 않으면 잘 못 썼을 텐데 말이야.
Dorcus? It is impossible to use one properly without good skills.
흥! 가이로트 군단 따위만 없었으면 도쿠스 따위!
Hmph! If Gairot Force wasn't getting in my way, Dorcus is nothing to me!
말은 잘 하네! 내 페퍼캣에게 구해진 주제에!
You sure talk big! You're just rescued by my Peppercat!
뭐, 뭐야?! 근데 키쿠히메, 너 누구 편이야?
W- what?! By the way, Kikuhime, whose side are you on?
ぎく|헉
그래, 걔한테 부탁이나 하고!
Yeah, you've been asking him for things recently!
♩ 이기면 됐지, 우리는 스크류즈! ♪
♩ Winning is everything! We are Screws! ♪
얼버무리지 마!
Don't dodge over!
잇키 군?
Ikki?
코쿠류라는 아이, 뭐라 했어?
What did Kokuryu say?
로보틀은 이기는 게 전부라고.
Winning is everything in Robattles.
잇키 군은 어떻게 생각해?
And what do you think about that, Ikki?
아니에요! 절대.
Not at all! Never.
메다로트, 단순한 다투는 도구가 아니에요!
Medarot is not a simple tool for quarreling!
그렇지?
You know it.
메타비하고 내게 있어 로보틀은 프라이드에요!
To Metabee and me, Robattles are the pride!
저널리스트의 피가 들끓어! 반드시 내가 밝힐 거야! 수수께끼의 메다로터의 정체!
The blood of journalist is boiling! I will be the one to discover the true identity of the mysterious Medarotter!
저, 정말이에요?
R- really?
어? 너 누구였지?
Huh? Who were you, again?
아, 그러니까, 전학생으로...
Again, I'm a transfer student...
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
아버지의 소중한 가방을 회사까지 가져가게 된 잇키와 메타비.
Ikki and Metabee were asked to take their father's bag to his company.
도중 뜬금없이 긴카이의 앙심을 산 잇키는 문답무용의 로보틀에 말려든다.
During that, Ikki bought Ginkai's grudge with a weird reason, he was dragged into a Robattle without question.
게다가 키쿠히메나 은행 강도까지 나타나서, 땅과 하늘에 대추격전이 펼쳐진다.
Moreover, Kikuhime and a burglar has appeared too, and a big pursuit is on the sky and ground.
과연 잇키는 약속 시간을 지킬 수 있을까?
Will Ikki make it in time?
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 택배 대소동
Next time on Medarot: Spirits! Uproar over Delivery
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!